我们要玩捉迷藏游戏 奖金$5万美元
We are playin' hide and seek for $50, 000.
这里有10个玩家 最后一个被找到的人获得$5万美元现金
There's 10 of them. Last one found gets the $50, 000 in cash.
你们有20分钟的时间藏身
You have 20 minutes to hide.
什么？
What?
19分钟
19 minutes to hide.
那只是一秒钟
That would be a second.
谁最后被找到谁就把钱留下 我不在乎是哪位
Whoever's found last gets to keep the money. I don't care who it is.
开工
Let's do this.
我不知道我是想和别人一起还是远离所有人
I don't know if I wanna be with people or away from everyone.
我不知道哪一个更让人费脑筋
I don't know which one's more nerve racking.
我要便便 我要便便
I gotta poop. I gotta poop.
现在不是时候
This is not the time.
我今早醒来 带上10个朋友和$5万美元并告诉他们藏起来
So, I woke up this morning, grabbed 10 of my friends and $50, 000 and told 'em to hide.
这就是我一天的内容
That's the extent of my day.
我想知道钱德勒藏在哪里？
I wonder where Chandler's hiding?
好了 我要去拉屎了
All right, I'm gonna go poop real quick.
我去 这不能锁？ 开玩笑的吧？
Dude, this doesn't lock? Are you kidding me?
这座建筑有数百个房间 成千上万的藏身之处
This building has hundreds of rooms and thousands of hiding spots,
所以 我不可能一个人找到他们
so, there's no way I can find them on my own.
所以我会和克里斯一起寻找
So, me and Chris are gonna be working together.
我们得制定个策略 克里斯
We need to devise a strategy, Chris.
你应该用你的眼睛 我用我的眼睛
You should use your eyes and I use my eyes.
听起来像是个可靠的计划
That sounds like a solid plan.
出发
Let's do it.
我想知道谁的藏身之处最蠢
I wonder who has the dumbest hiding spot.
我躲在剧院里
I'm hiding in a theater.
就像又回到高中一样
It's like high school all over again.
嘘 没人会知道
Shhh no one will know.
我和杰克（Jake）现在正躲在T台上
Me and Jake are currently hiding in the catwalk.
我们同时出现
We both showed up at the same time.
我们就藏在这里 一起
We're just gonna be here, together.
这有一个宝箱 我可以藏在这里
So, there's this treasure chest. I can hide in this.
我要蹲下来在这里呆一会儿了
I'm gonna hunker down and stay in here for a while.
再见各位
Bye guys.
我们把梯子弄走了 所以没法知道我们在哪儿
We got rid of the ladder so there's no way to tell where we are.
我们在这上面 我们做到了 希望能赢
We are up here. We did it. Hopefully win it.
朋友们 你们要么拿着$5万美元走人 要么什么都拿不到
Guys, you can walk away with $50, 000 or nothing.
还有一分钟
There are one minutes left.
记住 钱德勒 在我们开始挑战之前你不能出去
Remember, Chandler you can't get out until we start the challenge.
嘻哈
Dab.
只剩一分钟了 祝我好运吧
One minute left guys, wish me luck.
我是这里的学生 所以我知道所有的藏身地
I'm a student here so I know all of the hiding spots.
那个位置很好
The good ones, that is.
30秒
30 seconds.
30秒 我和本找了一个地方
30 seconds. Me and Ben found a spot.
如果他们让我们离开 我们就分道扬镳
If they tell us to move, we're gonna go our separate ways,
但在那之前 这里是个好地方
but until then, right here, this is a good spot.
你觉得这个地怎么样？
What do you think about this spot?
这是个好地方
It's a good spot.
很好吗？
Pretty good?
时间到 准备好了吗 我们来了
Times up. Ready or not here we come.
我认为一个好的策略是沿着所有的走廊走 然后我们进入所有的房间
I think a good strategy would be to just walk down all the hallways and then afterwards we go in all the rooms.
可以
Okay.
哦 那是个很好的藏身之处
Oh, that would be a great hiding spot.
嘿 德雷克 有人在这里
Hey, Drake, someone's in here.
什么？
What?
逮到了
Got him.
有10人 我们还没找到人
There's 10 people. We haven't found anyone yet.
好吧 这是地下室
All right, this is the basement.
我们先从这个房间开始 然后在所有的房间里慢慢来找
We're gonna start with this room and we're gonna work our way around all the rooms.
不管谁在这个房间 你都完了
Whoever's in this room, you're done.
我想后面那个角落里有人
I think there's someone in that corner back there.
啊 没人
Awwwww, man.
老弟 看看这个地方
Dude, look at this place.
不会吧
No freakin' way.
我们发现钱德勒
We found Chandler.
不 不
Nooooooooo.
好了 来吧钱德勒 你得进监狱
All right, c'mon Chandler, you have to go to jail.
我是第一个？
Am I the first one?
是的 你是第一个 第一被逮出局的
Yes, you are the first you really are the first one out You're the first one out.
你是第一个被发现的 你今晚要待在监狱里了
You were the first one found, you must now spend the night in jail.
我很高兴地告诉大家钱德勒被找到了
I am happy to report that Chandler has been found.
还有九个
Nine to go.
你躲在显眼的地方 却不管用
You hide in plain sight and it doesn't work.
一个倒下 还有九个
One down, nine more to go.
我们来了
We're comin' for you.
这栋楼里有个电影院 而我们才到了二楼
This building has a movie theater in it, and we're only on the second floor.
这里有很多地方可以躲
There's so many places to hide in here.
我向你保证有人藏在其中一个位置上
I guarantee you there's someone hiding in one of these seats.
我找到了一个梯子
I found a ladder.
这座大楼很大
This building is huge.
还以为这里肯定有人
Thought for sure someone would be up here.
说实话 我们还在这里真是个奇迹
Honestly, it's a miracle we're still here.
他们要把我们俩都干掉
They were about to take both of us out.
朋友们 我们现在在三楼
Oh, we're on the third floor guys.
不知怎么的 我们上了楼
Somehow we went up a floor.
阿布拉卡达布拉 没有
Abracadabra, nope.
谢谢致电 吉米·约翰斯服务
Thank you for calling Jimmy Johns.
我可以定个外卖吗？
Can I make an order for delivery?
是的 我饿了
Yes, I'm starving.
非常感谢 太棒了
Thank you so much, thank you, this is amazing.
我们走吧
Let's go.
吉米和克里斯就在我旁边
Jimmy and Chris are right beside me.
把这个弄掉
Take this off.
有办法进去吗？
Is there a way to get in it?
他们真的碰到了我藏身的箱子 却说没有办法进入
They literally hit the box I'm in and said there's no way to get in.
我们从未检查过这个舞厅
We never checked this ballroom.
哇 这个舞厅里可以玩很多球
Wow, you could have a lot of balls in this ballroom.
呃 呃 呃
Eh, eh, eh
等一下 我听到了什么
Wait a second, I hear something.
只是我赢了$5万美元 原谅我
It's just me winning $50, 000, I'm sorry.
你怎么知道这地的？
How did you know about this?
怎么回事？老弟
What in the world dude?
我以为肯定有人藏在这里
Thought for sure someone would be hiding here.
哇 这是什么？
Whoa, what is this?
你要我去看看
You want me to check it out
天呐 我们发现了一个秘密的通道
Dude, we just found a secret crevice.
老天
Dude.
泰 不不不不不
Ty, nooooooo.
来吧 我们去监狱吧 泰
C'mon, let's go to jail Ty.
给力 老兄
Dude, yes.
又一名选手倒下了
Another contestant has fallen.
只剩下八个了
Only eight remain.
钱德勒 我们给你带了个朋友
All right, Chandler, we brought you a friend.
好的 泰 请进
All right Ty enter.
监狱坏了
Jail broke.
我真是在瞎胡说
I was talkin' mad junk, too.
我还以为你找到了一个好地儿
I thought you found a good spot.
我也这么想的 老弟
I thought I had it too, man. Man.
好了 我们回来了
All right we're back.
这东西大约400磅
This things like 400 pounds.
我有三个 要一个吗？
I got three of 'em, want one?
好了
There go.
我们假设要么是泰勒（Tyler） 要么是杰克 要么是加勒特（Garrett）一直在给我们打电话
Our hypothesis is either Tyler, Jake or Garrett is constantly calling us.
他们可能在定位我们的位置
They're probably tryin' to find our location.
看到有人跑过 飞快的那种
Saw someone run across, like run run.
我们走吧
Let's go.
哦 他跑这了
Oh, there he is.
他去哪里？
Where's he goin?
可能要走楼梯
Probably gonna take the stairs.
他去哪儿了？
Where did he go?
只要电梯门一关上
As soon as this elevator door closes.
我们会追上你的 通话完毕
We're comin' after you, over and out.
让我们这样做
Let's do this.
只有$5万美元
It's only 50 grand.
我又不是要付账单什么的
It's not like I got bills to pay or anything.
我要去盘问钱德勒一些线索
I'm gonna go probe Chandler for some info.
钱德勒 能给我点情报吗？
Hey, Chandler, can you give me some intel?
给我一小勺情报
Give me a little scoop.
你要找谁？
Who you lookin' for?
不是一大勺 一小勺
Not like a giant scoop, a small scoop.
尖锥形的小勺子
One that sinks in the cone.
是向上还是向下
Is it up or down.
我们在几楼？
What floor are we on?
二楼
Two.
罗杰 我拿到了内幕消息
Roger, I got the inside scoop.
我能得到什么？
What do I get?
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
克里斯 克里斯 克里斯
Chris, Chris, Chris,
可能已经在行动了
might already be on the move.
我要饿死了
I'm gonna starve.
我们要找个新地方
We are gonna find a new spot.
是不是有人 碰巧 藏在你桌子底下？
Is someone, by any chance, hiding under your desk?
需要检查一下
Have to check.
好吧 你明白了
Okay, you're clear.
克里斯 我想我在这发现了什么
Chris, I think I found somethin' over here.
等等 只是我自己一个巨大的版本
Wait, it's just a giant version of myself.
这东西挺酷的
This things kinda cool.
这让我想起了我们和尤图兹（You Tooz）合作出售的的新产品
It reminds me of the new figures we're selling in partnership with You Tooz.
我时间有点紧 因为我在找人 所以我会让未来的我介绍尤图兹
I'm a little pressed for time'cause I'm finding people, so, I'm gonna let future me tell you about You Tooz.
在我们继续之前
Before we go any further,
我要告诉你们我们新的收藏玩具
I need to tell you about our new collectable toys.
你看 我们下个月要花几百万美元 我也想养活钱德勒
You see, we're spending millions of dollars next month and I wanna feed Chandler.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
这些是我们尤图兹的巨型版本 我们要做的是限量版
These are giant versions of our You Tooz which we're gonna doa limited edition run.
这里有一个有趣的事实 如果你买了克里斯的玩具 克里斯会得到钱
And, here's a fun fact, if you buy a Chris toy, Chris gets money,
如果你买了钱德勒的玩具 钱德勒就能得到钱
and if you buy a Chandler toy, Chandler gets money.
还有 买我的玩具 我可能还会把钱给克里斯或钱德勒
And also, buy my toy and I'll probably give the money to Chris or Chandler still.
这些都是按照我们想要的方式设计和建模的
These were designed and modeled exactly how we wanted.
我是说 钱德勒穿着和玩具同样的衣服 我们都没告诉他这么做
I mean, Chandler's literally wearing the same thing and we didn't even tell him to.
钱德勒 多少钱？
Now, Chandler, how much are they?
29 99美元
$29. 99.
什么是免费的？
And what's free?
你会买吗？ 买
And, are you gonna buy, yes.
另外 随机三个买了我们的尤图兹的人会得到一张金奖券
Also, three random people that buy one of our You Tooz will get a golden ticket.
如果你得到这张巨大的金奖券 我们会把它送到你家里
If you get this giant golden ticket, we will deliver this to your house
我们可能会让你拍个视频 我不确定
and also, we might let you be in a video, I dunno.
限量版 已上线
Limited edition, they're out now.
去买 买 买 买
Go buy. Buy, buy, buy.
你可能会出现在视频里 谁知道呢？
You could be in a video, who knows?
去买吧 结尾我会提醒你的
Go buy and I'll remind you at the end.
我们回去继续捉迷藏
Let's go back to hiding.
克里斯 这是个大房间
Chris, this is a big room.
这里一定有人
Someone's gotta be in here.
不在那里 不在那里
Not there. Not there.
检查 没有
Check, no.
上面没人
No one's up there.
我们在这里检查一下
Let's check up here.
你觉得我们在这里能做什么？
What do you think we can do in here?
我要到后面去
I'm gonna get behind here.
我们刚刚发现了一个全新的领域
We just discovered a brand new area.
我都不知道就是这里
I didn't even know this was here.
这些是运动传感器浴室
These are motion sensor bathrooms.
当我们经过走廊的时候 这个运动传感器已经被触发了
This motion sensor was already triggered when we came down the hallway.
我能听到吉米的声音 他来了
I can currently hear Jimmy, he's coming.
我们在冰箱里
We're in the fridge.
我发现你了
I found you.
噢 是的 是的
Oh yeah, yes.
好的 来吧
All right, here you go.
感觉怎么样 伙计们？
How's it feel, guys?
老实说 感觉很棒
It feels great, honestly.
哦 是的 老兄
Oh, yeah, dude.
哦 我听到了
Oh, I heard that.
来自通风口
Came from the air vent.
-你再做一次 -不
-You do that again, -No.
我们怎么还没找到维京人？
How've we not found Viking yet?
我知道 他很大块头
I know. He's huge.
但是 公平地说 我们还没去过每个房间呢
But, to be fair, we haven't even gone in every room yet.
因为我们真的需要找人 所以我要打作弊牌
Because we really need to find people, I'm gonna have to play a cheat card.
在接下来的10分钟内 你们都必须移动到一个不同的楼层
You all have to move to a different floor than you currently are on within the next 10 minutes.
我们要去搜查 我甚至会给你一个提示
We are gonna be scouring. I'll even give you a hint.
我们现在在二楼 好运
We're currently on the second floor. Good luck.
这与其说是一个暗示 不如说是一个确切的地点
That was less of a hint and more of an exact location.
但是 我喜欢你的风格
But, I like your style.
好的 我在去的路上
All right, so I'm on the way.
拿着我找到的尤图兹
Got my You Tooz I found.
我得换层楼了
I gotta get to a different floor.
吉米刚用无线电通知我们 说我们得换一层楼
Jimmy just radioed us and told us that we have to go to a different floor.
如果我们发现电梯里有人呢？
What if we found someone in the elevator?
那会很搞笑的
That would be hilarious.
花了一段时间（电梯）才到
It took awhile to get up here.
地下室的时候也是
It was at the basement, too.
电梯没开 有人在里面
It's not opening. Somebody's in there.
快 快 快 快 快
Go, go, go, go, go.
走 跟着他
Go, follow him.
这有一瓶水 有人渴了
There's a bottle of water. Somebody got thirsty.
我要准备好冲刺了
I gotta be ready to sprint.
错的
wrong way.
哦
Oh
该死 老铁 我听见有人在电梯里咳嗽
Darn it. Dude, I heard someone coughing in the elevator.
它停在这一层
It stopped on this floor.
逮到你了
Gotcha.
天啊 你怎么看到我的？
oh man, how did you see me?
加勒特被找到了
Garrett has been found.
重复一遍 加勒特被找到了
I repeat, Garrett has been found.
欢迎来到监狱
Welcome to prison.
所以 我们必须考虑一下
So, we have to think about it.
马库斯（Marcus）小个子 他能适应较小的空间
Marcus is smaller. He can fit in smaller spaces.
啊 啊 啊
Unh, huh, hul.
老兄 我要办它
Dude, I'm callin' it.
等等 等等
Hold up, hold up.
不会吧
No freakin' way.
有人在这里过
Someone was in here.
-不可思议 我打赌当我们检查时有人就在这里 -卧槽
-No freakin' way I bet you they were in here when we checked -No.
吉米和克里斯就在我旁边
Jimmy and Chris are right beside me.
我们早些搬的时候很重
When we went to move that earlier it was heavy.
现在移动它就像一根羽毛
Moving it just then was like a feather.
先前有人在里面
There was someone in there earlier.
我们快没时间了
We're runnin' outta time.
我们得做点什么
We need to do somethin'.
你觉得我们能不能再搞一次hut hut hike 420？（FNL赛场信号）
Do you think we can pull another double whammy, hut, hut hike 420?
注意 我们肯定快没时间了 你们还剩下很多人
Attention, we are definitely running out of time and there's still a lot of you left,
所以 我需要你们去一个你们现在不在的楼层
so, I'm gonna need you guys to go to a floor that you are not currently on.
你们有10分钟 好运
You have 10 minutes. Good luck.
他们可能都在行动
They're probably all on the move.
来吧
Let's do it.
嘿
Hey.
那就是我藏的地方
That's where I was hiding.
你知道他们会在楼梯上等着
You know they're gonna wait in the stairs.
我也是临场发挥 老兄
I'm wingin' it dude.
到这个点了 我真的只是想要运气
I'm literally just tryin' to be lucky at this point.
我也是
Me too.
我现在的藏身点可能是整个地方最亮的
My current hiding spot might be the brightest spot in this whole place.
我不知道该去哪里
I had no idea where to go.
电梯灯亮着
That light was on.
现在 我们在玩等待游戏
Now, we play the waiting game.
电梯移动了 有人叫了电梯
We're moving. Someone called the elevator.
你为什么要进电梯？
Why did you go in the elevator?
我们逮住你了 为什么要选电梯？
We got you why did you go in elevator?
不 不
Noooooo, no.
一箭俩沙雕
Two at a time.
噢 我的天啊
Oh my gosh.
来了个特别的 买一送一
They were havin' special, we got two for one.
目前有六人在监狱 也就是说你们只剩下四个人了
There are currently six people in jail, which means there's only four of you left.
你们中只有一个人能拿到$5万美元
Only one of you are gonna walk away with $50, 000,
所以希望你们能藏好
so I hope you guys hide well.
找到这个尤图兹 你被奖励了两千美元 又一次？
By finding this You Tooz, you're now awarded two grand, again?
四千美元 全因为这些尤图兹
Four grand all for these You Tooz.
哦 吉米 我放弃了
Oh, Jimmy, I give up.
赛姬 快五万四千了我要躲在椅子里
Psyche, it's about to be 54 grand and I'm about to hide in these chairs.
你觉得他会来这里找我吗？
Think he's gonna look for me down here?
这很冒险
This is pretty risky.
以后再见
See ya later.
我们进退两难
We have a dilemma.
我们还剩下一个小时 还有四个人
We have one hour left with this giant building and there's four people that remain.
我想我们需要制定一个计划
I think we need to devise a plan.
要是我们叫他们都到同一层楼里去呢
What if we told 'em all to go to a single floor.
剩下的四个人 我们还有一个小时的时间
To the four of you that remain, we have about an hour left.
我们得加点料
We need to spice some things up.
所以 我们要把范围限制在两层
So, we're gonna limit the range to two floors.
你有10分钟的时间去二楼和三楼 你需要躲在那两层楼里
You have 10 minutes to get to floor two and three and you need to hide on those two floors.
他们只是叫我换楼层
They just told me to move floors.
所以我们现在在二楼
So, we are on the second floor right now.
我们要回到剧院三楼的那个地方
We're actually gonna go back up to that third floor spot in the theater.
吉米找到我们比较困难 所以我们得动一动
So, Jimmy's havin' a hard time finding us, so we have to move.
我在剧院的三楼找到了新的藏身处
I found my new hiding spot, floor three, in the theater.
这里非常非常黑 他们可能忽略掉我
It's very, very dark back here. They could overlook me.
我希望如此
I hope they do.
我们可以做到
We can do this.
我相信我们
I believe in us.
我不 这些人真的很善于躲藏
I don't. These people are really good at hiding.
我们回剧院吧 肯定有人在这里
Let's go back to the theater. Someone's definitely in here.
该死
Dang it.
不 不 不 不 不 不
Nooooooo. Noooooooooo. Nooooooo.
我很失望
I'm so disappointed.
不过 那地方真不错
That was so good spot, though.
嘿 看起来你找到了一些尤图兹
Hey, it looks like you got some You Tooz back there.
对 我找到小钱钱的
Oh yeah, I got Chandler.
你知道钱德勒的尤图兹最棒的地方是什么吗？
You know what the best thing to do with Chandler's You Tooz is?
哇
Wow.
买我的尤图兹 它更好
Buy my You Tooz, it's better.
他说了
He said it.
我之前在箱子里
I was in the chest.
是你 你猜对了 就说是雅克（Jacob）
You Yeah, you called it I said it was Jacob.
我们有一个新朋友给你
We have a new friend for you.
哦 错了
Oh, noooooooo.
还有三个 来把他们吓跑
Three more. Let's scare 'em off.
克里斯又来了 真是个吵闹的男人
oh, there's Chris again. What a loud boy.
我们找到雅各了 所以你们只剩下三个人了
We found Jacob, so only three of you remain.
吉米刚在广播里说只剩我们三个人了
Jimmy just said on the radio that it's only three of us remaining.
我想我们找到了一个很好的藏身之处
I think we've got a really good hiding spot.
就像在百叶窗后面
It's kinda like behind some blinds.
我来了 我来了
I'm comin' I'm comin'.
哦 不 不
Oh, noooooooo
什么？ 你找到了谁？
What? Who'd you find?
不 马库斯
No, Marcus.
我找到你了 马库斯
I found you Marcus.
马库斯 不
Marcus, no.
他真的是 说马库斯 对不起 然后我就看到你赶紧跑了
He literally goes Marcus, I'm sorry, and then I just see you just bolted.
我们找到一个新成员 进来吧
We found a new member, c'mon in.
不 不
Nooooooooooooo
哦 老天爷啊
Oh my God.
我只想赢得我的第一个挑战
I just wanna win my first challenge.
擦干你的眼泪 孩子
Wipe your tears, son.
伙计 你差点就成功了 这不是我的错
Dude, you almost had it. It's not my fault.
只是因为游戏的名称
It's just the name of the game.
你的头发好柔软
Your hair's so soft.
还剩下两个人
There's two people left.
杰克·韦德尔（Jake Weddle）和本·马龙（Ben Malone）
Jake Weddle and Ben Malone.
我们找到马库斯了 也就是说你们还剩下两个
We found Marcus, which means two of you remain.
韦德尔先生 本先生 你们俩现在竞争$5万美元
Mister Weddle, Mister Ben, you two are now competing for $50, 000.
我希望我能赢 我真的希望
I hope I win this thing. I really do.
我不会被发现的 我要拿那笔钱
I am not getting found. I am taking that money.
现在只剩你们两个了
Now, since there's only two of you left,
你们俩都得移动到三楼去
you both have to migrate to the third floor.
第一个找到的失败 另一个将得到$5万美元
First one found loses and the other one will get $50, 000.
他们限制地点在三楼
They're confining it to the third floor.
我在三楼 所以我哪儿都不用动
I'm on the third floor, so I don't have to move anywhere.
我的电池快没电了 我在移动中
My battery's almost dead. I'm on the move.
我现在处于公开 我现在暴露了
I am out in the open. I am exposed right now.
我们现在从二楼到三楼 本和杰克藏身的地方
We are now ascending from the second floor to the third, where Ben and Jake reside.
我们从这里开始 我们要来个扫荡
Let's start off here. We're gonna do a sweep.
我们要走遍每一个房间 想办法解决问题
We're gonna hit every room and work our way around.
哦 我看到他了
Oh, I see him.
韦德尔 不 我看见你了
Weddle, no I saw you.
走那条路 我往这边走
Go that way. I'm goin' this way.
维德尔没有
Weddle no.
维德尔
Weddle.
我早就知道了 我太累了
I've known all along. I'm so tired.
我从下午三点就没吃过东西了
I haven't eaten since three p. m.
杰克 你的裤门也开了 不需要雪上加霜了
Jake, your fly is also down not to add insult to injury.
我们不要告诉本
Let's not tell Ben.
我们应该回家吗 不管本？
Should we just go home, forget about Ben?
是的 我想我们该走了
Yeah, I think we should probably just head out.
怎么了？
What up?
老弟 那是个好地方
dude, that's a good spot.
本 出来吧
Ben, come on out
这地方真的好
How good is that spot?
$5万美元捉迷藏游戏的获胜者是 本
The winner of the $50, 000 game of hide and seek is Ben.
我们得让韦德尔进监狱
We need to let Weddle into prison.
到属于我的地方
To where I belong,
这就是监狱里的孩子
this is what prison's like kids.
好了 本 现在我要尴尬地在所有人面前把奖金递给你
All right Ben, now I'm gonna awkwardly hand you the money in front of everyone.
也许你该给他们买点东西 我不知道
Maybe you should buy them some stuff, I dunno.
订阅 希望你喜欢 再见
Subscribe. I hope you enjoyed. Goodbye.
那真是一段美好的时光
It was such a good time
现在我真的可以给我的家人和所有的一切一个美好的圣诞节了 你懂得
and now I'm gonna be able to actually give my family and everything a good Christmas.
我真的很兴奋
I'm really excited.
好的 本 祝贺你
Well, Ben, congratulations.
好好享受你的$5万美元吧
Enjoy your 50 grand.
谢谢你 朋友
Thanks, man.